<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FeatherNotes</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_notes">EditNotes</string>

    <string-array name="hintQuestionsArray">
        <item>Who was your childhood hero?</item>
        <item>Who was your favorite teacher in School?</item>
        <item>What was your childhood nickname?</item>
        <item>What was the first company I have worked for?</item>
        <item>What was the first book I have read?</item>
        <item>In what city did you meet your spouse/significant other?</item>
        <item>What is the name of your favorite childhood friend?</item>
        <item>In what city or town was your first job?</item>
        <item>In which city did I got married?</item>
        <item>Where were you when you had your first kiss?</item>
        <item>What is your School Name?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="passCodeActions">
        <item>Forgot Passcode</item>
        <item>Change Passcode</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_despo">despo</string>

    <string name="credits">
        \nThis app uses following open-source libraries:\n\n

        # android-about-page\n
  [https://github.com/medyo/android-about-page]\n\n

The MIT License (MIT)\n
Copyright (c) 2016 Mehdi Sakout\n\n

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:\n\n

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n\n

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.\n\n


        # Junge-Regular (font)\n\n
        Copyright (c) 2011, Cyreal (www.cyreal.org),\n
with Reserved Font Name "Junge".\n
This Font Software is licensed under the SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1.\n
This license is copied below, and is also available with a FAQ at:\n
http://scripts.sil.org/OFL\n

    </string>

</resources>
